Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs UP012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs
1977 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Media Advocacy Board
UP012
1.8 Linear Feet
12 Digital Object(s)
1 Web sites
This collection contains issues and the archived website of Hemispheres, a journal that addresses social, economic, political and legal issues, both contemporary and historical, through the framework of international relations. Articles are research papers written by undergraduates.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Hemispheres: The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs and Web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Hemispheres, a journal that addresses social, economic, political and legal issues, both contemporary and historical, through the framework of international relations. Articles are research papers written by undergraduates. Some later issues include interviews and photo essays on international topics. Hemispheres was originally published annually by the Tufts Council on International Affairs, an undergraduate student group. It is currently part of the Media Advocacy Board.
This collection is missing issues from 1983-1984 (volume 8), 1989 (volume 13), and 1992 (volume 16).
The collection also contains web crawls to document the publication's web presence.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
- Hemispheres, The Tufts University Journal of International Affairs, 1977 -- 2021; UP012.001; 1.8 Linear Feet; 12 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of the journal Hemispheres. It addresses social, economic, political and legal issues, both contemporary and historical, through the framework of international relations. Articles are research papers written by undergraduates. Some later issues include interviews and photo essays on international topics. Hemispheres is published annually by the Tufts Council on International Affairs, an undergraduate student group.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Hemispheres, 1977; UP012.001.001.00001; Tufts Council on International Affairs (Box 1)
    First issue, Spring.
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - Hemispheres, 1978; UP012.001.001.00002; Tufts Council on International Affairs (Box 1)
    Spring.
    Volume
    2
  - Hemispheres, 1979; UP012.001.001.00003; Tufts Council on International Affairs (Box 1)
    3
  - Hemispheres, 1980; UP012.001.001.00004; Tufts Council on International Affairs (Box 1)
    4
  - Hemispheres, 1981-05; UP012.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    5, 1
  - Hemispheres, 1982-05; UP012.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    6, 1
  - Hemispheres, 1982 -- 1983; UP012.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    Fall-Spring.
    7, 1
  - Hemispheres, 1984 -- 1985; UP012.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    9, 1
  - Hemispheres, 1986 -- 1987; UP012.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    10
  - Hemispheres, 1987 -- 1988; UP012.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    11
  - Hemispheres, 1988 -- 1989; UP012.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    12
  - Hemispheres, 1990; UP012.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    14
  - Hemispheres, 1991; UP012.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    15
  - Hemispheres, 1993; UP012.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    17
  - Hemispheres, 1994; UP012.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    18
  - Hemispheres, 1996; UP012.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    20th Anniversary Issue.
    19
  - Hemispheres, 1997; UP012.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    20
  - Hemispheres, 1998; UP012.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    21
  - Hemispheres, 1999; UP012.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    22
  - Hemispheres, 2000; UP012.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    23 [mislabeled XXIV}
  - Hemispheres, 2001; UP012.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    24
  - Hemispheres, 2002; UP012.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
    25
  - Hemispheres, 2003; UP012.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    26
  - Hemispheres, 2004; UP012.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    27
  - Hemispheres, 2005; UP012.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    28
  - Hemispheres, 2006; UP012.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    29
  - Hemispheres, 2007; UP012.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
    30
  - Hemispheres, 2008; UP012.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
    31
  - Hemispheres, 2009; UP012.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
    32
  - Hemispheres, 2010; UP012.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
    33
  - Hemispheres, 2011; UP012.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
    34
  - Hemispheres, 2012; UP012.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    35
  - Hemispheres, 2013; UP012.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    36
  - Hemispheres, 2014; UP012.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
    37
  - Hemispheres, 2016; UP012.001.001.00035 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    39
  - Hemispheres, 2018; UP012.001.002.00001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    41
    Open for research
  - Hemispheres, 2019; UP012.000041 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    General
    42
  - Hemispheres, 2020; UP012.000042 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    43
  - Hemispheres, 2021; UP012.000043 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    44
- Web crawls, 2015 -- 2020; UP012.002; 1 Web sites
  Quarterly web crawls of the Tufts Hemispheres website crawled by DCA, as part of the Student Organizations web collection, to document the presesence of Tufts University student organizations on the web.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Student Organizations web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/6387
  - Tufts Hemispheres, 2015 -- 2020; UP012.002.00001; Media Advocacy Board
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.